Yeah, we're about to load
them onto the truck now.
Yes, tomorrow, I promise.
What could be going on this late...?
Damn it... Huh...?
(In Russian) Hello.
Wha...?
(In Russian) Goodbye.
What kind of psycho uses a weapon you
have to recover every time you use it?
Shut up, you idiot.
Relax, she doesn't
understand what we're saying.
Hey, Major! Is it true that Russian
women will sleep with any American guy?
Asshole.
You may be ex-GRU,
but now you're in it for the money.
So what's the price for
a night in your bed, eh?
Hey, cut it out!
Yes? What? OK...
Ms. Radinov!
It looks like the boss
has another job for you.
For an additional fee, of course.
Another hit?
"Thank you for calling Gunsmith Cats."
"We're unable to take
your call at this time."
"Please leave a message
at the sound of the beep."
Would you mind explaining why
you dragged us all the way out here?
We're the ones who caught you, remember?
This is a bad place to try
to get revenge, you know...
As far as we're concerned,
your case is closed...
...so what did you hope to accomplish
by making the ATF guys leave the room?
Ah, well... sorry about that...
Hey, are you listening to me?
Damn, he cut the microphone!
I'll get it.
I'm not safe here! You gotta get me out!
And just where would you find a safer
place? You're in an ATF safe house!
Washington, why isn't it safe here?
You don't understand... I know too much.
I'm a sitting duck in here.
That's why the ATF has
five agents out there at—
No, listen to me!
You can't trust the ATF!
Washington, time's up.
Open the door!
Get the spare key!
Right...
Washington! Open up! Washington!
Hold on... could you at least
please take this watch? It's a Rolex.
All I'm asking is for you to deliver this to
my daughter. Here, I'll give you her address.
Now wait a second! Why should I do...?
This is all I've got to pass on to her.
Please, Rally!
Wait a second!
We're not finished talking yet.
No, I've heard enough.
But...
Excuse me.
Rally...
I was telling you the truth.
You'll find out sooner or later. But
I won't be around when you do.
After everything he's been through, this
was all he had left... That's kinda sad.
Sheesh! You're too soft, May.
Why's that?
Because you took a job that won't pay.
Oh, I didn't hear you
raising any objections.
That's not the point.
By the way, May, have you
been practicing the new timings?
Huh? Yeah, I've been working on them.
I'm on the last song now.
Want to go over it?
Sure.
Get ready... Huh?!
That punk bitch!
I won't forget that face!
Rally...
Damn it!
They dumped this extra shit on me.
Aw, at least it kills time.
Next up...
Huh?
The mayoral election is
around the corner. Huh?
State senator Edward Heinz declared
his support for the total eradication...
...of illegal weapons and drugs in
a joint press conference with the ATF.
We all know law-abiding
citizens don't need these things.
I'm just trying to promote
some common-sense solutions.
Where's the camera? Ah.
Fellow citizens!
I, Edward Heinz, promise you that...
...together with George
Black of the ATF...
Heinz has been busily
promoting his positive...
Well,
the boss never misses a PR opportunity.
Hey, are there any other
visitors scheduled for today?
No, not that I know of.
Hey Bill, what's going on... Huh?
Stop! I'm warning you!
Drop the gun!
W... Wait!
I know something about the organization.
Don't kill me! My people...
Man! Five agents down...
Looks like there is a spy in the ATF.
Hey, did you hear the rumors about Bill?
Hear what?
Can you explain this, Bill?
It's hard to believe that you...
What? Sir, you can't think that I...
Bill, you're off the case as of now!
But sir! You don't really think
I'm guilty, do you?
Someone is clearly trying to frame you.
So I need to handle it!
Bill... this isn't a battlefield.
Going it alone won't win you any medals.
Understand?
Yes, sir...
Yes. This is a good time.
Yes, I eliminated the first target.
I've already checked
the intel on the next two.
I must say, I'm surprised to learn
of an American woman of such skill.
Yes, I got it. Heroin sells
for a very high price in Russia.
By the way, I have received
no intel on the fourth target.
I see... So, he will be surprised
when his own partner has him killed.
Are you sure this is the place?
Yeah, that's what the paper says.
Well, I guess we'd better go see.
I wonder how old his daughter is.
Around 10 or so, I guess.
Number 6. This is it.
Good eve... Good eve...
What do you want?
Nothing... Nothing...
A fake address and a fake Rolex...
I wonder what he was really up to?
It's got to mean something.
That's not good enough, May. You got us
into this, so it's on you to figure it out.
Now hold on! This was as
much your idea as mine... Ah!
Heh! Geez, May! Chill out!
I wasn't serious.
Hey, Rally, that's my pop.
Give it back!
Hey, Rally! Aaah!
Uh... May... are you all right?
I'm not talking to you. Huh?
In any case... it's pointless
to keep thinking about this.
I guess we'd better drop it for now...
right?
Working hard, eh? Please, have some...
Uh... well... I don't think I...
I don't need to hear your excuses, Bill.
Our business with you is over, right?
If you've got time to bug my house again, you've
got time to arrange that license you promised.
This investigation isn't over yet, Rally.
I can't do it without your help, honest!
Stop acting, it's pointless.
You're a fool if you think
we would ever trust you!
Oh, that's cold.
But you win, we're leaving.
Yes, sir.
Did you have enough
time to get it all set up, May?
Of course! Piece of cake!
Naturally...
I'm ready here.
Roger.
I should have known...
Damn!
The way to crack this is to figure
out what these things really are.
Could it be a phone number...? No...
It's not a bank account number,
but it could be some sort of code...
Hrmmmmm...
Hey, did you notice anything strange
the day you caught Washington?
Huh?
We did it.
Yeah, our rhythm was perfect.
Are you even listening to me?
Ah! Sorry!
But you might be right.
Maybe there was a clue...
Oh...! He had internet access!
He did? That's it!
I'll bet this is an internet
address and access code!
Hey... there's something carved here!
What?
Look...
What's this number?
Of course!
Huh? Huh?
This is a secret code for a site
on the network. Huh? Huh?
Watch carefully.
First, we enter the first letter of each
word in the address, plus the phone number.
That's it! That's the picture
Washington had on his monitor!
Bingo! Now, we enter the number
on the back of the watch.
Nailed it!
That's incredible, Becky!
What an idea...
hiding data in a porn site.
But what kind of data is this?
Wait a second.
Let me look at these dates...
Let's see...
Ah... The weapons they're selling
were all previously seized by the ATF.
Rally, you can sell this data
for a very high price, but...
But first, we'll need proof.
Exactly.
May... ready to roll?
Absolutely!
I knew you would be!
Wait! Let me make some printouts!
Heh... You print out there, and
I'll print out here, Miss Becky.
Bill!
How come you're still here? I
don't want to hear that you're still...
No way! I'm writing up my reports.
I've been putting them off for too long.
Well, all right... But remember, you're
supposed to be assisting Frank! Understood?
Aye aye, sir!
Is this the right place?
The shipment should
have arrived here last night.
Hey, let's do this later.
You can't back out now!
Sorry, Becky, you'll have to stay here.
Sorry, Becky, you'll have to stay here. Of
course. I wouldn't come even if you asked.
Oh, I see.
Pretty serious security for
a yacht club during the off-season.
It's a good thing we left
Becky back in the car.
May...
Let's go.
Wow, the mother lode!
Uh huh.
Hold it right there, you two...
The boss told us you'd be dropping by.
You two look pretty hot.
Come on over so we
can get a good look at you.
How about we take good
care of you before we kill you?
Hey, hurry it up!
It's her...!
Shit...
Huh...?
Hey, that was cutting it a bit close...
Bill! Not you again! This sucks!
What the hell are you doing here?
Well, was I even a bit helpful?
This might be another set-up!
Huh? That's a good one.
I happen to share your opinion
about the trustworthiness of the ATF.
You tapped into our computer,
didn't you? You snake!
May?!
May!
Rally, get in!
I'll drive!
Rally! Hey, take me with you! Rally!
Hey!
Let's move!
May, get the message!
Rally! OK, time to bust a move!
That's her! Music... start!
One... Two... Three...
Get off of me!
You little bitch!
Rally, don't go crazy!
Tell that to her!
Oh no you don't...!
Becky, can you see May?
Hold on... Huh...?!
Yikes!
Fuuuuccck!
That punk bitch!
Becky, open the window!
Rally!
This ain't over yet!
Damn you!
One more verse. Then you're mine!
Well,
at least this makes it easier to shoot!
You're dead!
Bitch!
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Zero!
Oh... Shit!
Hah... Nice catch...
Oooh! Are you totally insane?!
Rally! Look!
May, just what did you do?
Boy, that was quick!
Rally...
We did it again, May!
But it's not over yet...
Huh? Huh?
There's more work to do...
...before this business is over.
Finally, it's time to get
back to business as usual.
Well, I guess I'll be
going on a date with Ken...
Hey, you two! You'd better not
relax yet. Radinov's still alive!
What?!
What?! Oooh! I guess that ominous
sense of foreboding was for real.
We're in trouble, Rally! This whole
incident's turning into a bottomless pit!
The next episode of Gunsmith Cats!
Chapter 3! "High Speed Edge."
If Radinov wants a one-on-one duel to
the death, that's what she's going to get!