Yeah, I'm about to load
them in the truck right now.
Yes, tomorrow. I promise.
What could be going on this late...?
Hello, comrade.
Wha...?
Goodbye.
Eh... What kind of a psycho uses a weapon
you have to recover every time you use it?
Shut up, she'll hear you.
- Ah, she doesn't speak any English.
- Really...
Hey, Major! I've been told that you Russian
women will sleep with anything American.
- Is it true?
- Idiot.
Heh. See... what did I tell ya.
Here...
You may be ex-KGB, but
money's your master now.
So what's the price for
a night in your bed, eh?
Cut it out, you jerk!
Yeah? What? Right...
Ms. Radinov?
It looks like the boss has
another assignment for you.
For a separate fee, of course.
Who's the hit?
"Thank
you for calling Gunsmith Cats."
"We're unable to take your call at this
time, but if you require our services..."
"...please leave a message at the
sound of the beep."
OK, Washington, would you mind explaining
why you called us all the way up here?
We're the ones that caught you,
remember?
Yeah, and I don't think this is a place
you'd pick for your revenge, either...
Hey, as far as we're concerned,
your case is closed...
...so what do you hope to accomplish by
making the ATF people leave the room?
Yeah!
Hey, are you listening to me?
- Damn, he found the microphone!
- I'll get it.
I'm not safe here! You gotta get me out!
And just where would you find a safer
place? You're in an ATF safe house!
May's right. This is about as
safe as you're gonna get.
You don't understand... I know too
much. I'm a sitting duck in here.
That's why the ATF has five agents that—
No! Listen to me!
You can't trust the ATF!
Washington, your time's up.
Open the door!
- Get the spare key!
- Right...
Washington! Open the door! Washington!
Hold on... I've got an idea.
If you can't help me, take my Rolex.
All I'm asking is for you to deliver this to
my daughter. Here, I'll give you her address.
- Wha...? Now wait a second! Why should I do—?
- Please, I'm begging you.
This watch is all I've got to
leave behind. Rally, please!
- Time's up.
- Wait a second! We're not finished talking yet.
- No, I've heard enough.
- Huh? But... you can't...
C'mon, May.
Rally...
I was telling you the truth back there.
You'll find out. But of course, I'm not gonna
be around to say, "I told you so," am I?
After everything he's been through, this
was all he had left... That's really sad.
- May, you're too soft.
- Why's that?
Because you accepted a job
that won't pay us a dime.
Oh sure, like you didn't see
the whole thing happen.
That's not the point.
By the way, I meant to ask, have you
been practicing those new moves?
Huh? Of course, they're easy. I'm
working on the "showdance" pattern now.
- Want to go over it? - Sure.
- Right...
- That bitch is dead! I won't forget that face!
- Rally...
Damn it! I already put this stupid
thing in once before.
Aw, at least it kills time.
And in the local news, the race
for the mayor's office is heating up...
...and state senator Edward Haints
is throwing fuel on the fire.
In a joint press conference with George Black of
the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms...
...the senator declared war
on illegal weapons.
I don't think anyone believes that the American
way of life has to include this dangerous menace.
I'm just doing what any red-blooded
American would do.
Where's the camera? Ah.
My good friends! Edward Haints
believes in your family's safety...
...and with the help of George Black
of the ATF, I'll give it to you.
Haints has been making
similar speeches...
Well, you can't say our boss doesn't know
which side of his bread the butter's on.
Hey, are there any other visitors
scheduled today?
No, uh, not that I know of.
Hey Bill, what's— uhh... Hold it!
I'm warning you!
Stand back! I'll shoot!
Put the gun down!
What...?!
No, don't kill me! I got evidence
about the organization.
Please don't do it. My partner will
take care of any problems—
- Geez, what a mess.
- Man...
Five agents at once...
- Do you think it's true about there being a spy in the ATF?
- I dunno...
- Uh, did you hear about Bill?
- Hear what?
Here's the printout. You want
to tell me what this means, Bill?
Well? Tell me the truth!
But, sir! You can't think that I...
Those guys were my friends!
I want you off this case, now!
You can't! You don't really
think I'm guilty, do you?
I'm finding it hard to deny that there's
a major leak in your investigation.
Then let me handle it!
Bill... this isn't a field of honor,
it's a war.
You want to win medals or battles?
Do you understand?
Yes, sir...
Ah, it's you.
Your timing is good.
Yes, I've already handled the first one.
I have the data on the
next two right here.
I must say, I'm surprised to find
an American woman of such skill.
Yes, I've got it. Heroin is very
dear in Mother Russia.
By the way, I have not received
data regarding the fourth one.
I see... So he would not be expecting
to be killed by his own partner.
- Are you sure this is it?
- Yes, that's what the paper says.
Well, I guess we're going in.
I wonder how old
his daughter would be?
Around 10 or so, I guess.
Room 6. This is it.
Good eve... ning.
What the hell do you want?
Nothing...
Hmm... A fake address and a fake Rolex...
I wonder what he was really up to?
There's got to be something.
"Something's" pretty vague, May, but since
you got us into this, it's your problem.
Now hold on! This was as much
your idea as mine... Ah!
Hey, chill out, May!
I wasn't serious.
Dammit, Rally! Gimme back my pop!
I'm not kidding, I'm getting angry!
Uh... May... are you all right?
I'm not talking to you. Huh?
Well... In any case... I think it's pointless
to go on investigating this thing anyway.
I mean, hear me out. Is there really any reason why
we can't just leave everything right where it is?
- - Wha...?
- Delivery!
Working hard, huh? Try the sausage.
Hah.. well... I, er, don't—
I don't need to hear your excuses,
Bill.
And by the way, I've already filled
my half of our bargain.
If you've got time to bug my house again, what's
the holdup on the license you promised me?
This investigation isn't close to being
finished! Rally, I can't do it without your help!
I find that hard to believe,
I really do.
And if you think we'd ever trust a
snake like you again, then you're nuts!
Oh, that's cold. Right you win...
we're leaving.
Yes, sir.
♪ PIANO FADES
Well, did you have enough time to
get everything all set up, May?
Of course! Piece of cake!
Impressive!
- I'm ready here.
- Roger... Huh?
I should have known...
The way to crack this is to
figure out what these things really are.
Maybe it's a phone number...
or maybe not.
It's not a bank account number,
but it could be some sort of code.
Hey, did you guys notice anything
strange on the day you caught Washington?
- We did it.
- Yeah, that was perfect rhythm.
Are you listening to me?!
- Err...
- Ah! I'm sorry!
You know, maybe there was a clue.
Now, let me think...
Yeah! He was working on his computer!
He was? That's it!
I'll bet this is an internet address
and an access code!
Hey... there's something carved here!
- What?!
- Look...
What's this number?
I've got it!
This is a secret code for
a site on the network.
Watch carefully.
I'm going to type in the initials of the
name, address, and phone number.
- Hello!
- That's it!
That's the picture Washington
had on his monitor!
Bingo! Now, type in the number
on the back of the watch.
C'mon, C'mon, C'mon...
- We did it!
- Oh, that's incredible, Becky!
It's brilliant... they hid their data in
plain sight by disguising it as a website.
But what kind of data is this?
Wait a second.
Let me look at these dates...
Yes! Here's the day that the ATF made
the raid on the warehouse! - Yeah!
And here's the weapons that were seized.
This information is priceless.
But first...
- But first, we'll need evidence.
- You got it!
Well, I think we can handle that...
right?
- Absolutely!
- Such enthusiasm!
Hey, wait a second! At least wait for me
to finish making these printouts!
You print out there, and I'll print
out here...
I just love computers.
Bill!
What are you doing here in the middle
of the night? You're off the gun case!
Oh, yes, of course! I'm just organizing
my reports. I was too lazy before.
Well, all right... But remember, you're
supposed to be assisting Frank! Understood?
Aye aye, sir!
Is this the right place?
Well, the shipment should have
arrived here last night...
- I don't know... Hey, let's do this later.
- You can't back out now!
Sorry, Becky, you'll have to stay here.
It's all right. I wouldn't come
if you asked me.
I know...
Pretty serious guard for a yacht club
in the off-season, don't you think?
It's a good thing we left
Becky back in the car.
Mmm-hmm... You ready?
C'mon!
- Wow, the mother lode!
- Oh, yeah!
Hold it right there!
The boss told us to be on the lookout
for some hot-looking broads...
...so I think you'd better turn
around slowly...
...and let me get a good
look at your face.
Who knows, maybe we'll have a little fun before we kill you.
Hey, hurry it up!
Grenade!
It's her...!
Well that was pretty close, pussycat.
Wh... Oh, no! Not you again. This sucks!
All right, Bill, what're you doing here?
Well, I saved your life.
Maybe, or maybe this was all a set-up.
That's good.
At this particular moment, I don't trust
the ATF any more than you do.
Huh...? So you went and bugged our
computer too, didn't you? You snake!
- May?!
- Rally!
Ahhh! May!
- Rally, get in!
- Wait up!
- I'll drive!
- Hey, take me with you! Rally!
- What?! Hey!
- Let's move!
Hold on!
C'mon, wake up!
Rally! Alright, it's showtime!
That's her! Music... here we go!
One... Two... Three...
Cut it out!
You little rat!
Hey, Rally, don't go crazy!
Tell that to her!
Oh no you don't...!
- Becky, can you see May?
- Hold on... Ahhh...!
Yikes!
That was dirty pool!
Now I'm pissed!
Becky, open the window!
Rally!
It's not over yet!
Damn! Not again!
A few more beats...
You won't get away!
Well,
at least this makes it easier to shoot!
What...? You little bitch!
You die!
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Zero!
No!
Hang on!
Thanks... Nice catching!
What? Are you totally crazy?
Look out!
May, just what did you do?
That was good work!
Rally...!
We did it again, May!
- Hmm... But it's not over yet...
- Huh?
We've got a little more work to do...
...to finish this.
Finally, it's time to get
back to business as usual.
Ho-ho! Well, I guess I'll be
going on a date with Ken.
Hey, you two, you'd better not start relaxing yet.
Radinov's still alive! - What?!
Damn! I guess that ominous sense
of foreboding of mine was right!
This whole incident's turning
into a bottomless pit!
It's the next episode of
Gunsmith Cats! Chapter 3!
"High Speed Edge."
If Radinov wants a one-on-one duel to
the death, that's what she's gonna get!