Politics... Economy... Crime...
Insanity... Family... Chaos... Weather...
Your daily life... Media Break.
A typical commuter hour becomes
a scene out of a nightmare.
A burning car falls off a bridge
following a high-speed chase.
Daniel Morgan has the story.
Immediately after driving off
the drawbridge, the doomed vehicle...
...burst into flames before crashing
into the icy river below.
Although rescue crews were able
to retrieve the car with a huge crane...
...no bodies have yet been discovered.
George Black, director of the ATF
Division in charge of the investigation...
...told us that the bodies may have been
swept downstream by the river.
In conjunction with
several civilian operatives...
...we were investigating a gunrunning
operation when the incident occurred.
However, I would like to point out that
this incident only serves to prove...
...that the movies are the only place where amateur
vigilantes can successfully combat criminals.
The names of the civilians involved in
this incident have not yet been revealed.
But we know who they are, don't we?
You oughtta be ashamed of yourselves!
Yes, sir.
I hadn't been back from my first
vacation in years for five minutes...
...when the phone started
ringing off the hook.
You've really gone and done
it this time. They want blood!
Aw, come on, Kate. You're blowing
everything way out of proportion.
Oh, she's not exaggerating.
Just take a look outside.
We've already had to send out extra
patrols to cover the extra traffic...
...and the weekend
hadn't even started yet.
It wasn't our idea, you know.
That's right, Roy. We're not the ones who
caused this; we're innocent victims ourselves.
So, why did you blow up the ATF agents
assigned to protect you?
That investigator, Collins, said
that you refused to cooperate...
...and made it impossible for
the ATF to watch over you.
- Ooh! That snake!
- Give me the file. - Right!
We received this
information from the ATF.
She appears to have entered
the US via Canada about 3 days ago.
That's her, all right! Roy, who was she?
- Yeah!
- Natasha Radinov, ex-KGB, ex-Special Forces.
Currently believed to be
a freelance assassin.
She's also known by the code name
"Bloody Pierce."
She's a human murder machine,
trained in every possible lethal skill.
And until now, she's never failed
to take out her assigned target.
She's not a woman. She's a Terminator, Rally.
And someone's paid her to take you out.
- Huh?!
- You think she's still alive...?
Why don't you let us
worry about Radinov?
I'm ordering you to take this bag, go
home immediately, and behave yourselves.
- Huh...?
- Huh? What is it?
Ah, just some stuff my wife
picked out. C'mon...
I'll give you an escort...
to the back door.
Toodle-loo...
Rally, please don't work too hard.
- Yeah, yeah...
- See ya 'round, Roy.
Uhhh... I don't think this is
gonna be very good for business.
Yeah,
this whole thing was a waste of time.
Well, I'd say this is a good sign
she's still alive.
Hello, Gunsmith Cats.
- What do you mean? Yeah...
- Ugh! What kind of cheap crap is this?!
Does he think we're a bunch
of Japanese tourists?
Calm down. He meant well... Huh?
- Hey, who was that?
- State senator Haints' office.
It seems the senator wants to give us
an award during his campaign rally.
- Huh...?
- State senator Haints? You mean the same Haints who's been running for mayor?
Oh man, I bet he'll have the media there
and there'll be a huge party in our honor.
Wow,
maybe some big talent scout'll spot me!
- You're weird...
- Yeah...
Now, what were you saying?
I didn't like his attitude...
He said now that this weapons case
had been closed...
...they wanted to use it make Haints'
weapons reform an issue.
Closed the weapons case? Doesn't
he know that Radinov is still alive?
Well, since we haven't found out
who's pulling the ATF's strings...
...this is our chance to speak
to someone higher up.
Sorry, but I'm going to have to decline.
I wouldn't be able to do business if
everyone knew what I looked like.
What? But it's such a waste...
I'll leave all the
talent scouts for you.
But Rally, don't let your guard down.
She could attack anywhere, at any time.
Hah! If that's the case, then I'll ask
her to pay for the repairs on my Cobra.
Yeah...
Ugh! Not that one!
Hmm...
Nah, this one isn't right either...
Hey, Rally, which one do you
think looks better?
Umm... Either one, I suppose.
Geez,
you could at least look at me first!
May, it really doesn't matter what you wear.
What's important is what's underneath it all.
You don't have anything that's
bulletproof, do you?
Don't worry about me. And by the way, Rally, why
don't you wear those high heels I bought you?
- Huh...?
- I didn't buy them just to sit in your closet.
Those are mine?
Uh... Eyah!
See? They look good on you.
Eyah... That's entirely besides
the point! Oh boy...
May, if I wear these things,
I won't even be able to move.
Then the men will just have to
come to you instead, Rally.
Oh sure, right.
- Huh...? - See? They're here!
- Very funny, May.
Rally, why don't you take them off now?
Uh... Oh, yeah...
Who's there...?
Freeze!
- Huh?
- Rally, it's me, Bill! I've got to talk to you.
Ugh! Not you again...
- See, a man did come!
- May!
Just kidding!
- Shut up!
- Come on pussycat, open up!
Leave! I don't want to talk to you,
you snake-in-the-grass!
The investigation's going to be
cancelled if we don't do something.
Rally, please!
I really need some cooperation here!
Sorry, snake-lips.
I've decided to go over your head.
So I'll be talking to a certain
VIP tomorrow, without you!
VIP? What do you mean?
It's none of your business, anyway!
- I've got to get up early, so why don't you slither home!
- Rally...!
Huh...? What?
'Scuse me sir, but do you have any
business with these two ladies?
Look, I'm Bill Collins, an ATF investigator.
I need their cooperation for an investigation.
You don't have to show me your ID card.
My orders are to not let anyone come
near this house, not even the president.
Okay, I give up!
Hey, if you see the president,
give him my regards.
I'll tell him you said "hello."
If that's what you get from wearing high
heels, I'm switching to combat boots.
- Hmm...
- Bill! Where on Earth have you been?
You're never here when something
important happens.
Cathy, I'd give you a great big hug, but
unfortunately both of my hands are busy.
We don't have time
for your fooling around.
Take a look at this. I've been going
over the ATF telephone records...
...and I don't like
what I've discovered!
Number 6?!
Yes. That's a safe house we were
supposed to have shut down.
Grrr... So who's still using it?
George Black? No way!
You mean my boss is the one
behind this? So where is he?
He turned in a vacation request
yesterday. He's already gone.
Don't lose your composure, kitten.
I'll take care of this!
Great work, kid. A real achievement!
- Bill... - Now, Cathy... promise me
you won't tell anyone else.
- OK, kid?
- Right.
Great! Look... lets do lunch sometime.
I love you, honey!
Oh... Bill! Awww...
Radinov? Radinov!
You're in here, aren't you?
Ah, there you are. That's great, uh...
I was really getting worried about you.
My, my...
the director of the ATF is here.
Look,
I can't keep fooling them much longer.
Listen, Radinov. You've got to take me
with you when you leave the country.
Hmph!
How very self-centered and foolish.
Hey, I'll pay you whatever you want.
I've got lots of money. Yeah...
Hmm... Right. Your orders?
Huh? Hey! Is there somebody else
in the building?
Yes, I suppose we'll have to take care
of the problem.
No! Wait a second!
I won't tell anybody anything!
Radinov, for god's sake! Tell him!
Did you hear that?
Right...
Radinov... Aahh...
Please... Please help me...
It looks like the chief!
What happened to him?
Jody, stay back!
What's that doing there?
A beginner's level booby trap. However,
the person who set it is no amateur.
I'd suggest that we
be extremely careful.
Huh...? Jody!
I pushed the redial. Maybe we'll find
out who the last person he talked to was.
Are you deaf? We're dealing with a professional!
Don't touch anything until it's been checked!
Don't worry. Nothing happened.
Oh, it's connecting.
"You have reached Eddie Haints' office.
Our office is closed now—"
Who is Eddie Haints?
A state senator and
a friend of the chief's.
And if the chief called him from here...
...then Radinov, the chief, and
Haints are a team. Ohh...!
Rally said she was going
to go meet some VIP!
Jody, don't touch anything else! Got it?
Hey, Bill, wait a minute!
Hey... where's the fire, big guy?
A pro... I knew it...
Rally...
Great. That's it guys!
I should not have stayed here
as long as Black wanted me to.
However, I have one thing to finish
first... or should I say, two things.
You mean Vincent and Hopkins?
I wouldn't be adverse to letting
some of my boys handle them.
That will not be necessary.
You won't have to pay me, either.
So it's gotten personal, has it?
Nyet. This is a matter of pride.
Mr. Haints, we've got a request for
a television interview this afternoon.
Tell them they'll have to wait.
I'm not going to speak to anyone until
all of these loose threads are eliminated.
Right.
On behalf of Mr. Haints, I'd like to thank you
all for braving the rain to come here today.
- Right now it's looking like the ceremony will be delayed about 3 hours.
- Here, take this...
I don't get it. They told us to be here
at the crack of dawn.
Are we just going to sit in this
stupid tent until the sun sets?
- Ohhh, I'm cold...
- Politicians are always like this, Rally.
Well,
we could leave if that's what you want.
We can't do that. Unless I get this license
thing cleared up, we can't reopen the shop.
Aw man, my feet are turning into ice.
Ohhh! This sucks!
Not only that, it's disappointing too!
Excuse me, ladies...
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Watch your hands!
I'm sorry for acting so suspicious, but
we are responsible for Mr. Haints' safety.
Hmpf! I'll do it myself, thanks!
- There!
- Hmm... That's quite a selection.
I'm afraid that we'll have to hold on
to all of these for you.
I'll hold on to those,
if you don't mind.
- And who might you be?
- Roy Coleman, Chicago PD.
- Do you have a problem with that?
- Heh... I suppose not. I'll see you later.
What a jerk!
If Haints hires thugs like that, I don't
think I'm looking forward to meeting him.
For sure!
Thank you for waiting, ladies and gentlemen!
And now, without further ado, Edward Haints!
Eddie! Eddie...!
Hello, everybody!
Thank you.
Thank you, my fellow citizens.
And now, I'd like to introduce you
to my special guests!
Yes, these are the brave young women whose
actions foiled a band of ruthless gunrunners!
Miss Rally Vincent and Miss May Hopkins!
What's the matter, ladies?
Feeling a little nervous?
I have a special award to present
to these lovely heroines!
This plaque is a symbol
of our appreciation...
...as we, the people, commemorate
your bravery and courage.
- Rally, May, please step forward.
- Don't worry, I won't bite.
Here, Michael...
Hold this mic. Thank you.
- Rally, run! Rally!
- Huh?
That's her!
C'mon May, let's go!
Rally! Wait up!
What's going on?!
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh! He's the ATF agent in charge
of the gunrunning case!
- What?
- It's all a big trap.
I've got to stop Rally...
Don't worry.
I'm with the Chicago Police.
- Roy, I got my guns back!
- Wait! Rally!
That was too close. Now I'm
gonna take this fight back to her!
Well?
Yeah, it's working. OK, May, you enter from
the back. I'll go in through the front.
- Ready?
- You bet!
- Let's go!
- Okay!
I see her...
Hold it right there!
Let me warn you, that bulletproof coat
of yours won't protect you this time.
Make one false move,
and you'll be missing a head!
Get your hands up
where I can see them!
Now turn around slowly!
I said turn around slowly!
I've got the drop on you, Radinov!
You have the drop on me, but you won't
shoot me in the back.
You lose!
No! Rally...! Huh?!
May!
I have beaten you, Rally Vincent!
I'm going to make you pay
for this little nick.
I know a lot about pain, bounty hunter,
and I'm going to share it all with you.
I won't let you die quickly. After all, I
can only hurt you while you are still alive!
Rally...
Get ready to run...
What the...?
Where are you?!
Downstairs...
Two... One...
Yes, I'm standing in front of Grant
Park, where just a few moments ago...
...a series of gunshots were fired at mayoral
candidate Edward Haints during a campaign rally.
At the moment, the suspected gunman
is holed up inside the museum...
Rally... hold on!
I'm doing all right.
How about you?
Hey, I'm doing just fine.
I just wish I could use my hands.
It's a good thing
I already set up some traps in advance.
Did it work?
What the hell?
That's enough! Gray, I'm leaving.
Fortunately, the media is concentrating
on Radinov right now, but...
What do you mean by "fortunate"?
Listen! That crazy Russian psychopath
was shooting at me too!
I want her out of the picture! Huh?
Radinov!
What in the hell are you doing here?
And what was the big idea of pointing a
gun at me while I was up on the stage?!
I'm severing our business relationship, and I
want you to return the heroin I already gave you.
C... Calm down, Radinov...
I didn't mean that.
Heh... You understand, right?
That's right! We've got to stick
together, you know.
Yeaaah!
I don't believe it! The gun control
candidate... with a gun in his hand!
Stricter gun controls would mean you could
raise the prices for your illegal weapons, hmm?
- Well, did you get that?
- It's art.
No... What are you doing?
Turn off that camera! Turn it off!
I've been framed!
- I love this job!
- Get out of my way!
Edward Haints, you're under arrest.
No...
I was so close... I could have cleaned
out all the gangs and immigrants.
"I was so close...
I could have cleaned out..."
"...all the gangs and immigrants. I only
did it for the good of the American people!"
What a bunch of vultures!
That's just the way reporters are,
I guess.
The cost of freedom
is eternal vigilance.
At least it's over for now.
But still...
we were a little careless this time.
Yeah,
but I won't tell if you won't, May.
Fortunately,
she was a little careless too.
- Die!
- Can I make it?
My arm can't move!
Admit it, sometimes I'm useful.
I'm a real Eliot Ness, pussycat.
Not you again...
- Oh, ma'am, are you all right?
- I'm fine. I can get up by myself.
I have to be able to stand up for myself.
You've gotta be tough
to live in this town.
You said it!