An ordinary morning commute turned into a nightmare today when a shootout erupted during a two-car chase.
Daniel Morgan is on the scene.
As you can see, the suspect’s car plunged off the drawbridge into the canal, where it exploded, sending up a column of black smoke.
Although rescue crews were able to raise the car with a crane, no bodies have been found inside.
The ATF is leading the investigation.
Here’s ATF Director George Black, who says the bodies may have been carried off by the current.
Fortunately, with the cooperation of civilians, we were able to break up a gun-smuggling ring.
But let me tell you this.
The "vigilantes vs. criminals" plot where the former come out on top only works in the movies.
We're still investigating who were the civilians involved.
Indeed, I bet you didn't see it coming that the police would lecture you for this.
The moment I get back from my
first vacation in forever, this happens.
You're not making it easy for me, Larry.
Don't you think you've
gone a bit too far this time?
Come on, not you too, Kate.
You're blowing this way out of proportion.
She's not exaggerating.
Just take a look outside.
It’s the weekend—our busiest time—
yet we still have to rotate extra patrols.
It wasn't really our fault, was it?
That's right, Roy.
If anything, we're the victims in this.
So that's why you shook off your ATF guardians?
That agent, Collins complained that you made it impossible to protect you.
That asshole...
Give me the file.
Okay.
We received this
information from the ATF.
She appears to have entered the US
from Canada about three days ago.
That's her, all right!
Roy, who is she?
Nastasya Radinov, ex-operative for the Soviet special service.
Currently a freelance gun for hire.
Code name "Bloody Pierce."
It seems she was doing freelance hits
ever since when she was in the special forces.
She's a killing machine, trained in every lethal skill.
She's basically the Terminator.
You're up against one hell of an enemy, Larry.
So you think she's still alive?!
That's a worry for us.
Your job is to take this bag
and go home quietly.
What's that?
It's from me and my wife...
I'll walk you out the back door, our "heroes."
Larry, please don't go overboard again.
Yeah, I know.
See you.
So much for our chance
to make some money.
We just went through hell for nothing.
Ugh...
That's her sending us a challenge...
Hello, Gunsmith Cats.
What do you mean?
What on Earth is this?
Does he think we're Japanese tourists?
Calm down. He meant well... Huh?
Hey, who was that?
Senator Heinz's secretary.
He wants to honor us
during his campaign rally tomorrow.
Senator Heinz?
The guy who's been running for mayor...
That Heinz?
I bet he'll throw a huge party in our honor!
Ah... Whatever shall I do
if some talent agency recruits me?!
Look, you...
Now, what were you saying?
Anyway, he was very pushy.
With the smuggling case closed, he wants to use it to promote his gun prohibition campaign.
The smuggling case is closed?
Don't they know Radinov is still alive?
We still haven't caught the guy pulling strings for ATF.
This might be our chance to speak to the senator directly.
Sorry, but I'm going to have to decline.
It's bad for business if everyone knows what I look like.
What? But that's such a waste...
You can claim all my fame for yourself.
But Larry, don't let your guard down.
She could attack at any time.
When she does, I'll make her pay for all the repairs on my Cobra.
Hm... Not quite it either...
Hey, Larry, which one do
you think looks better on me?
Ah... Isn't it all the same?
Geez! Can't you at least look here?
It really doesn't matter what you wear.
Instead, you should worry more about your own safety.
Don't you worry about me.
By the way, Larry, try those heels.
I bought ones for you too!
Those are for me?
See? They look great on you.
That's not the point... Whoa...
There's no way I can run in shoes like these!
Maybe not, but they'll make the guys run to you.
Gimme a break, May!
See? They're here!
Don't be silly!
Larry, you can take them off now.
Oh, yeah...
Who's there?
Who're you?!
Larry, it's me!
It's Bill!
I've gotta talk to you.
Not you again...
See, they attracted a man!
May!
Just kidding!
Sheesh!
Larry! Come on, open up!
Humph! We have nothing to talk about with you!
As things stand, the investigation will be shut down.
Please! I need your help.
Too bad, but with or without you, we're going to cut a deal directly with a certain VIP tomorrow.
VIP? Who do you mean?
None of your business!
Either way, I've got to get up early tomorrow, so shoo.
But Larry...
Excuse me, sir, could you explain why you are here?
Look, I'm Bill Collins of the ATF.
I need their help with an investigation.
No need to show me your ID.
My orders are to not to let anyone approach this house, not even the president.
Oh well, I give up.
If you see the president,
give him my regards.
Will do.
Man or not man, I'm not interested.
Bill!
Hm?
Where on Earth have you been?
You're never here when
something important happens.
Cathy, I'd give you a hug and a kiss
but my hands are full.
We don't have time for silly jokes.
Huh?
Look at this!
I checked the phone records like you asked,
and look what I found!
Uh... Huh?
Number 6?
Yes. That's a safe house that was supposedly shut down.
So who's still using it?
George Black? No way!
So our boss is the true mastermind behind this?
So where is he?
He suddenly put in a leave request and walked out.
Don't worry, Cathy.
I'll take care of this...
Very well done! It's a huge breakthrough.
Bill...
Just promise me you won't tell anybody else yet. Deal?
Okay...
Attagirl.
We'll catch dinner together sometime.
Love ya, honey.
Ah... Bill!
Ugh...
Radinov? Radinov!
You're here, aren't you?
Radinov?
Phew, you're okay. That's a relief.
Why, it's the director of the ATF himself?
Look, I can't keep fooling them much longer.
Radinov, I'm begging you.
Take me with you.
So you think the world revolves around you?
No... I've got money, if that what it comes to.
Name your price and I'll pay it. So please...
So... what should I do?
I-Is there somebody else here?
Yes, it's best to dispose of him, it seems.
N-No, wait! I'll keep my mouth shut!
R-Radinov, please tell them!
Did you hear that?
Got it.
P-Please...
Help me...
Radinov...
What the hell?! B-Boss!
Geordi, freeze.
What's that doing there?
A simple booby trap.
After all, we're up against an expert in murder.
We can't be too careful.
Wha... Geordi!
I pushed the redial. Maybe we'll find out
who the last person they talked to was.
Didn't you hear me? We're dealing with a pro.
Don't touch anything until it's been checked.
But nothing happened.
Geez...
Oh, it's connecting.
"You have reached Eddie Heinz's office.
Our office..."
Who's Eddie Heinz...?
A state senator and a friend of the chief's.
A-And if he's connected to it too...
...then Radinov, Boss, and Heinz were working together.
The VIP Larry said she's meeting... Could it be...
Geordi, don't touch anything else!
Got that?
Hey, wait! Bill!
What's the big hurry?
Sh-She's... A pro... Larry...
OK. That's where we want it.
Just as Black said, I had better not overstay my welcome in Chicago.
However, I have one thing I need to attend to first.
You mean those two little girls?
I actually don't mind dealing with them myself.
That is not necessary.
This one I will do for free.
So it's gotten personal, has it?
Nyet. This is a matter of pride.
We've received a request for a TV interview.
Tell them I decline.
I would prefer to remain silent until we tie up all the loose ends.
Right.
Thank you all so much for coming
today despite the rain.
We will open the venue in three hours.
We're sorry to keep you waiting in this cold weather...
I don't get it. They told us to be here at the crack of dawn and sit under this tent until evening.
I'm so cold...
This is what you should
expect from politicians, Larry.
We could leave if you'd prefer.
We can't do that. We need that business license to reopen the shop.
Aw man, these pumps are all muddy too.
Brr! It's freezing.
Not what I hoped for at all...
Excuse me...
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Uh... Hey!
What are you doing?
It's not that we don't trust you,
but we have the senator's image to consider.
We can do it ourselves!
Incredible...
I'm afraid we'll have to hold onto these for you.
I'll take care of them.
And who might you be?
Roy Coleman, City Police.
Do you have a problem with that?
I suppose not. I'll see you later.
What a jerk!
If Heinz hires thugs like that, I doubt he’s one bit of angel himself.
No shit...
Thank you for waiting!
And now, may I present Edward Heinz!
Hello, everyone...
Yes, thank you.
And now, without further ado, I'd like to introduce our today's special guests!
Yes, our heroes who single-handedly
foiled a band of ruthless gunrunners,
Larry Vincent and May Hopkins!
What's the matter, ladies?
Feeling a little nervous on the stage?
I have a special award to present to these lovely heroes!
This plaque is a humble symbol of our appreciation for their bravery and courage.
Now, Larry, May, please step forward.
Don't worry, I won't bite.
Here, Michael, hold the mic.
Larry, run!
That's her! May, let's go!
L-Larry!
What's going on?! Hey, what happened?
Ah! He's the ATF agent who was in charge of the gunrunning case!
What?
I-It's a trap.
We've got to stop Larry and May.
Don't worry.
I'm with the Chicago Police.
Ah!
Roy! I took my guns back, no hard feelings!
Wait! Larry!
Bring it on!
I'll give you this one-on-one duel!
Well?
Yeah, it's working. May, you enter from the back. I'll go in through the front.
Ready?
OK!
Let's go!
Yeah!
There you are.
Hold it!
Just a warning: that bulletproof coat won't help you.
One false move,
and you'll be missing a head.
Show me those hands!
Now turn around. Slowly.
Have some dignity.
You'll lose if you don't show me your face!
Yet if you don't want to shoot me in my back...
You'll lose!
L-Larry!
May!
We meet at last, Larry Vincent.
I'll make you pay dearly for this little nick.
I want you to endure the same...
No, far more pain than this.
I won't let you die easily.
You'll know true agony before you go.
Larry...
Run...
Wha...?
Shit...
Downstairs?
And... cue!
Yes, I'm standing in front of Grand Park, where just a few moments ago a gunman opened fire on mayoral candidate Edward Heinz during his campaign rally.
At present, the suspect holed up inside the museum, currently closed for renovations.
Larry, hang in there!
Don't worry about me.
Don't you need help yourself?
I'm doing just fine.
Minus you hanging on my hands.
It's a good thing I prepped some traps in advance.
Hm...?
Right...
Got her...
Hm? What's that?
Hey, that's enough! Gray, I'm leaving.
Okay...
Fortunately, the media is concentrating on Radinov right now, but...
What's "fortunate" about it?!
Listen! That crazy bitch wanted to kill me as well!
We can no longer trust her...
Radinov?
What the hell are you doing here?
And what was the big idea of pointing your gun at me as well?!
We're done doing business with you!
And I'd better get the heroin I gave you back...
C-Calm down, Radinov...
I didn't mean that.
Yeah... You understand, right?
I mean... We're in this together, after all.
When campaigning with slogans such as “down with guns,” you don't point a gun at another person.
Tighter gun regulations mean higher retail prices, don't they?
Did you get it?
Perfectly.
S-Stop! What the hell are you doing?
P-Put that camera away!
What's going on?!
This is huge! Get moving!
Move!
Senator Heinz, you're under arrest.
I was so close to cleaning out all the gangs and immigrants...
I only did it for the good of the American people!
What the heck?! Hey, get the camera!
Record Heinz's face closely!
Okay...
They're coming out!
What a bunch of vultures.
That's just how reporters are.
To survive in this country,
we need to become much stronger.
But...
We're not very flexible, are we?
You could leave that out, May.
Ready?
I guess she's not very flexible either.
Die!
Get away!
What's going on...
I can't raise my arm!
Even I can be useful sometimes.
Not like Eliot Ness, but still...
If you say so...
Are you all right?
I-I'll live.
I can get up by myself.
I have to be able to stand on my own...
That's what it takes to make it in this town...