Hey, what's up... Janice...?
What? Who is this?
You're not Janice! Wrong number.
Huh? The train...
Ahh! No! Where is it? Where is it?
Uh...? Oh, shi—
Dammit, May! Learn how
to adjust those things!
Jailbreak... Illegal weapons...
You've been a bad boy, Washington.
You're no cop. Who the hell are you?
The name's Rally Vincent, bounty hunter!
They call me Minnie May!
There, we're all introduced.
Gunsmith Cats; thank you for calling.
What?! Becky, that doesn't make sense!
Well, Washington was arrested
on suspicion of drug smuggling...
...but when the feds busted his shop,
it was totally clean.
That's nuts. Why would he take off,
if he knew he wouldn't be charged?
You didn't ask me to find that out.
I just don't get it.
Hey, Becky, could you dig up some more
dirt on him? Something smells.
Will you pay me this time?
Bloodsucker!...Hmm?
Look, I've got a customer
in the shop. Later...
Oh, hello.
What can I help you with today?
Well, I've got a
custom job I want made.
A friend on the force, Roy Coleman,
sent me here.
- Oh... Could you fill out this form please?
- Uh, OK...
Hmm... Terrific...
Hey, you really ought to be more careful! Did
you realize you left a bullet in the chamber?
Uh, oops. My mistake.
Your form's filled out.
Thanks. I'm guessing
that you're a police officer.
You know, this'll make your gun heavier.
That's for my private collection. I'm in the
K-9 section, so I carry one of these puppies.
A revolver, huh? I'd suggest you bring
that in for maintenance soon.
- Sounds like you've got some loose parts to me.
- Er, I do...?
Oh... that's my partner calling.
Uh, you can call me at that
number if you'd like.
Hey, how about dinner?
Tempting... but I think I'll just call you
when your gun's ready. Say "Hi" to Roy for me.
A bulletproof heart,
just like I heard. See ya!
Come back soon!
- Boy! It's no wonder you're still single.
- No one asked you.
- You're not getting any younger, you know.
- Oh shut up! -
Hi... Huh?
Don't worry! I'm not dangerous.
William Collins, ATF. Bureau of Alcohol,
Tobacco, and Firearms, Special Investigations.
Hey Minnie, it's Agent 007-11.
We keep our books legal.
Oh, no. Don't worry.
That's not what I'm here for!
- Then, what?
- Hmmm... Can we speak frankly here?
I'd like your help on
a little sting operation.
What did you say?
What say we talk this over in
the back room? Hmm...?
So, let me get this straight... Jonathan Washington
doesn't smuggle drugs... he's a gunrunner?
Er, right. You see...
...the reason he skipped out was so he could find
a buyer to sell enough guns to post his own bail.
But of course, I caught him
before he could do that.
Well, why not let him escape again?
I'm afraid it's not that easy...
which brings me to why I'm here.
You want us to do business with him so
you can find out where the guns are.
Uh huh. Of course, I can't pay you
for your services, but I... Hey!
I'm sorry, but I don't
think we have much to discuss then.
The exit is over here!
Ah, bummer. I really didn't want
to resort to an investigation...
Just what are you saying?
All these firearms— you must have
a Class 3 license, right?
You don't have one?
And you, May Hopkins...
Illegal explosives, violation of
dangerous material handling laws...
Right... Lay down
your terms, you government worm.
If everything works out,
you can get your license...
...and a healthy deduction off
the taxes you'll own on each gun.
Well, I'm in no hurry.
Toss it around and, uh, let me know.
Thanks for the coffee.
Uh, oh yeah...
You ought to get this lock checked.
Au revoir...
They just left the shop.
Roger. I'm ready.
Just be careful.
Roger.
Hey! There's nothing to eat here!
Whaddya mean, nothing to eat?
I just went out and got dinner.
Don't be such an ingrate.
I'm really sick of Chinese food.
And I'm sick of the
pizza you always order!
I'm not that bad, and you know it.
But seriously, what do
we do about that ATF guy?
What choice do we have? If we don't do what
he wants, we'll both be wearing gray lingerie.
You don't sound like the Rally I know.
Can't we do anything?
Well, why don't you use some
of those feminine wiles of yours?
You've got a thing for middle-aged men,
right?
- Yeah...
- Well, at least I'm still young at heart.
Come off it, Rally.
That guy was a world-class loser.
Yeah, and his mom dresses him funny.
Oh, Kenny... Yes... Again...
Hey! This looks like a normal house.
Are you sure there're weapons in here?
Hey, man, trust me.
Let's just hurry up and do it.
Burglars?
All right!
Wow! It's the mother lode!
Yeah, if your mom's name
is Schwarzkopf.
Wow! Huh? Something for everyone!
Heh! What kind of a nut would
live in a place like this?
Hey, man! Take a look at this sucker!
Yeah! Forget about robbin' banks,
let's just go start a war!
Yeah, why not. Someplace tropical.
Three of them. Piece of cake...
Yeah...!
- Hold it! - Hmm?
- Where do you think you're going with those?
But Rally, they're smoke grenades.
No explosions in the house, May.
Now go back to your room.
Hey! The next room over is
filled with ammunition.
Cool. And just my gauge.
Man, you can't wait
to load that thing, can you?
Heh! I've been waiting
for a gun like this all my life!
- Huh?
- What the hell?
Crap!
Where are you?!
Huh? Wait! Don't go that way!
Huh? Wha...?
Freeze!
Hold it... This is a no-parking zone.
What do you mean, "Stay out of this"?
My, my, my... these...
Hello, girls.
Look, May, our guardian angel. Isn't it
funny how the ATF got here so quickly?
Hmph!
Now that hurt; we're the good guys!
Yeah... sure you are.
Of course, I couldn't help noticing...
this is quite a collection you've got here.
It'd be a real waste to have
to melt all these down.
- All right, already. We'll cooperate.
- What?
You will? Hey, that's great!
But first, let's get this straight.
I handle my end my own way.
No tails, no interference.
Hey, you got it!
Here, do you want to shake on it?
- I'd rather tongue a snake. May!
- Huh? - Let's go!
Ra... Rally!
Oh well,
at least you're wearing a clean pair!
Will you shut up?
So do you always visit
the guys you send up? Huh?
No, but most of the guys I arrest don't
have something I wanna buy.
Well, your timing really sucks, but...
Ah, OK.
Let's say I've got something.
I'll need a security deposit up-front.
Then we can talk details.
Just how big of a deposit?
Why don't you go ask the judge?
Oh, I gotcha.
Here's the deal. I just posted bail, so
Washington should be on his way out any time now.
Then, he'll fax me the time and place.
Good deal. You know, bringing you on
was one of my better ideas.
Can the compliments. Just remember
the terms of our agreement.
No interference, right?
Oh! Aw gee, Rally, would I break
a promise to my favorite pussycat?
Why am I not feeling reassured?
Was that nice? You're such a cynic.
OK. You have my word.
- What?
- The boss wants to see ya.
Terrific. I should have known
I couldn't keep this undercover forever.
Yeah, if you want to take it that
way. Right...
Come in.
You bellowed?
I want a full update on this gunrunning
investigation, Collins.
We've got three dead agents,
and I haven't seen a report in weeks.
- I've been busy.
- Right... So who do you have working undercover this time?
- No one.
- No one? What about your evidence?
Well, there's no evidence either.
You see, the way I got it figured
is that there's a leak...
...somewhere in the ATF.
You can't be serious! In this office?
I'm not really sure. If I had a name,
I'd have done something by now.
That's very... disturbing.
Yes, Priss?
You have a call from a state councilman.
I'll be right with him.
Hey, wait, Collins!
I guess I'm the logical one to go
undercover this time... Right?
Yeah, good idea.
- Hello! Yes, this is George Black...
- I'll be seeing ya.
Oh, yes sir.
It's good to hear from you.
Staying on top is such hard work.
Why are you always doing this
to me? Have you no consideration?
- You could have at least called me!
- What'd you say, Becky?
I said, why'd you take such
a stupid assignment?!
At least I could have gotten
you a better deal!
Look, I told you... He had the license,
and there were all those taxes.
- It's entrapment!
- Rally, you got a fax!
Oh, Becky, what're you doing here?
Oooh! Good question! It's obvious my
good opinion isn't worth anything here!
Hey, hey, I'll tell you what...
Why don't I buy you dinner?
No pizza, and no Chinese.
Alright, Rally! I thought we
were going out to dinner.
You and May can sit in the car
while I run an errand.
And after that, we can all
get something to eat.
Hey... do you need me to
help you with anything?
- Just stay in the car.
- Uh... why should I?
Oh, I see. You want me to
keep an eye on her.
- Bingo!
- Now wait a second here...
Slow down!
- Well, this is it.
- Oh, you're kidding...
I'll be right back.
- May, behave yourself.
- Mu Mch!
- Be careful, OK?
- Mwarry!
Who is it?
Rally Vincent. I'm here to see
Jonathan Washington.
- Alright, get in.
- Why, thank you.
- You're packing, right? Take it out slowly.
- Okay...
- Slowly!
- Right.
OK, where do you want it?
Give it to him.
- Hmm...
- What's next?
Anything else...? Hmmh?
Whaa?!
Does this count?
Ah... Right! Check her out.
- You're so thorough.
- Sorry! Just doing my job.
Watch your hands, buddy.
- Washington's up there... You. Go with her.
- Yes, sir.
I think he likes me.
Bitch... she's gonna be trouble.
- Yeah, what?
- I want the name of your decorator.
I did it myself. Well, you
actually showed up.
Of course I did! I didn't pay your
bail out of kindness, you know.
Speaking of which, the guys that took
my guns weren't exactly polite.
You'll get them back... just as soon
as you pass a little test.
- A test...?
- Yeah. It seems my boss is a little nervous about you.
- Mmm... Just what kind of test?
- Oh, it's no big deal. Here... c'mon.
- Who's he?
- Just some special agent.
He was snooping around outside. But
fortunately, my boss spotted him.
Cute, ain't he.
It's so great to be famous.
- Hey, I know him!
- Huh?
That's right, he actually tried to
blackmail me into helping him.
- Yeah, I thought so.
- Rally...?
Sorry about this, guy, but I really
don't like being pushed around.
- Well, what's the test?
- Here...
- Hmm?
- It's his gun.
You're saying you want me to kill him...
It's part of doing business.
Fuck! Hmm...?
What is this? So where are the bullets?
You don't expect me to club him to death
with this thing, do you?
Oops! Hey, you're good!
You know, not many people could tell
a gun's empty just by picking it up.
- Here...
- One? Glad you trust me.
My boss is nervous.
Well tell him to calm down. I want to
make this deal as much as you do.
Oh by the way, I'd like some proof
that you've got the merchandise.
No problem! I know... I've got a few
pieces over here.
Now here's a real handy little item.
C'mon. How about something
a little more conventional.
Don't worry. Every crate in this
whole warehouse is filled with guns.
Oh, perfect.
- Argh!
- What?!
Get him!
Hold it right there!
Uh! Let's talk this over, please.
Now do you see what can happen
when you're too suspicious?
Just take it!
Oh, no! All the lights went out!
Oh boy...
I've got a bad feeling about this.
- So now it's my turn!
- May? How'd you get loose?
No! Don't!
Come back!
Y'know, Rally, you really
had me worried there.
Serves you right for butting in.
Hey, just how did you get here anyway?
Hmm... Y'know, my mother
may dress me funny...
...but I'm a real Eliot Ness, pussycat.
Yeah... right.
You know what? They don't trust you!
Looks grim. It's too bad we
can't grow some wings.
Suit yourself. I don't intend to
wear a halo anytime soon.
What an optimist!
OK buddy... why don't you go first?
What're you doing? Jerk...
Over there!
Aaah! I'm outta here!
This sucks!
Locked! Well...
...I'll fix that!
Hmmm... "Eeny, meeny, miny, moe!"
Rally! Cover me!
You're not serious, I hope?!
Eliot Ness my... huh?
- Rally! You alright?
- I hate to gamble.
Two at once.
I knew she'd be trouble.
Maybe I should gamble more often.
I was shooting blind.
Rally, look in back of you!
Rally!
Uhh! Help!
- My gun!
- Rally!
Rally, it's me!
- May, look out!
- Bye bye!
- Rally!
- Idiot!
- Die!
- Bill!
Got it!
Not bad! I came in handy after all, huh?
Oh, sure! That was about the stupidest
stunt I've ever seen!
You think so?
Me too...
It's not over...
It's not over by a long shot!
- It's my turn!
- What...?!
Oh, crap!
I'm not involved with any of this.
Yes, we caught the whole lot of them.
What's your current situation?
What is your problem?
Why can't you stay out of trouble?
And if I hadn't shown up,
where would you be now?
I can take care of myself!
Oh, is that so? Oooh!
- Hey, both of you.
- This is all your fault!
Eh? What did you say?
The explosion left me a little deaf.
- What a jerk!
- Yeah, what rock did you ooze out from under?
Yep, I'm slime. Which reminds me, I've got one
more little job for you girls! How about it?
You're joking...
- He's serious!
- Outta my way!
When it rains, it pours.
Just when we thought we were finished
with this gun-smuggling business...
You wouldn't believe who contacted
us and asked us to help him escape!
We trust Bill from ATF...
about as far as we can throw him.
And there's this crazy
Russian running around!
You'd better be extra careful.
That Russian's a real psycho!
Rally, help me!
May!
Don't miss Gunsmith Cats,
Chapter 2: "Swing High"
Now you'll see some driving.